<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:ror="http://rorweb.com/0.1/" >
<channel>
  <title>ROR Sitemap for http://www.nzescape.com/</title>
  <link>http://www.nzescape.com/</link>

<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/</link>
     <title>New Zealand Tourism Guide, Tourist Attractions, Accommodation, Tours, Rental Cars, Campervans</title>
     <description>New Zealand tourism guide featuring tourist attractions accommodation in New Zealand plus information about places to visit, where to go in NZ tours, tourism destinations, transport options such as rental cars  and campervans.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>0</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/visiting-nz.html</link>
     <title>The best time to visit New Zealand, Visiting NZ, Visa, weather</title>
     <description>The best time to visit New Zealand including information about visiting NZ. Do I need a visa weather travel driving in New Zealand.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/transport.html</link>
     <title>New Zealand Transport Options, Getting around NZ, Getting about New Zealand</title>
     <description>New Zealand Transport Options Getting around New Zealand Getting about NZ.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/marlborough-sounds.html</link>
     <title>Marlborough Sounds Tourism Guide, Picton visitor information, attractions, accommodation</title>
     <description>Marlborough Sounds Tourism guide including Picton visitor information, attractions, accommodation and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/destinations.html</link>
     <title>New Zealand Destinations, NZ Visitor Destinations, Places to Visit, places to go</title>
     <description>New Zealand Destinations guide including information on NZ visitor destinations, places to visit, places to go in New Zealand.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/auckland.html</link>
     <title>Auckland Tourism guide, Information about visiting Auckland, travel guide</title>
     <description>Auckland tourism guide including information about visiting Auckland, travel guide.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/bay-of-plenty.html</link>
     <title>About Bay of Plenty Tourism Visitors Guide, Tauranga, Mt Maunganui, Attractions Guide, Whakatane Visitor Information</title>
     <description>About Bay of Plenty tourism visitors guide including Tauranga attractions, Mt Maunganui, Whakatane travel and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/the-coromandel.html</link>
     <title>The Coromandel Tourism Guide, Coromandel visitor information, attractions, accommodation, Cathedral Cove, Pauanui, Whitianga</title>
     <description>The Coromandel tourism guide including Coromandel visitor information, attractions, accommodation, Pauanui, Whitianga, Cathedral Cove and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/eastland-hawkes-bay.html</link>
     <title>Eastland / Hawkes Bay Visitors guide, Hastings tourism, Napier, Gisborne, visitor information</title>
     <description>Eastland Hawkes Bay visitors guide including Hastings tourism visitor attractions in Napier, Gisborne and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/northland.html</link>
     <title>About Northland NZ, Bay of Islands visitor Information, Paihia, Russell, Cape Reinga</title>
     <description>About Northland NZ including Bay of Islands visitor information, Paihia attractions, accommodation, Cape Reinga travel and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/rotorua.html</link>
     <title>Rotorua Tourism Guide, Visiting Rotorua information, attractions, accommodation</title>
     <description>Rotorua tourism guide featuring information on visiting Rotorua attractions, accommodation, transport and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/ruapehu-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Ruapehu Tourist Attractions Tongariro National Park Mt Ruapehu Visitor Attractions and activities</title>
     <description>Ruapeh tourist attractions guide featuring Tongariro National Park attractions activities Tongariro Crossing.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/taranaki.html</link>
     <title>Taranaki Tourism Guide, New Plymouth travel, visitor information, Mount Taranaki</title>
     <description>Taranaki tourism guide including Mount Taranaki attractions and New Plymouth visitor information.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/taupo.html</link>
     <title>Taupo Tourism Guide, Lake Taupo travel and visitor information</title>
     <description>Taupo tourism guide including Lake Taupo travel and visitor information.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/waikato.html</link>
     <title>Waikato Tourism guide, Hamilton visitor information, Attractions, Waitomo Caves, Accommodation, Cambridge, Te Aroha</title>
     <description>Waikato tourism guide including Hamilton visitor information, Waitomo Caves attractions, Hamilton accommodation and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/wellington.html</link>
     <title>About Wellington Tourism guide, Wellington visitor information, attractions, accommodation</title>
     <description>About Wellington tourism guide including Wellington visitor information, attractions, accommodation and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/abel-tasman-golden-bay.html</link>
     <title>About Abel Tasman and Golden Bay, Visitor attractions guide, Kayaking, Farewell Spit</title>
     <description>Information about Abel Tasman National Park, the Abel Tasman walkway, kayaking, visitor attractions guide, Golden Bay, Farewell Spit and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/akaroa.html</link>
     <title>Akaroa Tourism Guide, Akaroa NZ travel guide, visitor information</title>
     <description>Akaroa Tourism guide featuring Akaroa NZ travel and visitor information.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/blenheim.html</link>
     <title>Blenheim Tourism Guide, Wine Tasting, Winery tours, Blenheim Visitor Attractions, information</title>
     <description>Blenheim tourism guide including Blenheim visitor attractions, wine tasting winery tours and other tourist attractions.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/central-otago.html</link>
     <title>Central Otago Tourism Guide, Visitor Information, Attractions, Rail Trail, Cromwell, Clyde, Accommodation, Naseby</title>
     <description>Central Otago tourism guide including Alexandra visitor information along with Cromwell Attractions, accommodation in Central Otago, Clyde Roxburgh, Naseby and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/christchurch.html</link>
     <title>Christchurch Tourism guide, About Christchurch Visitor information, Attractions, Accommodation</title>
     <description>Christchurch tourism guide about Christchurch visitor information, attractions, accommodation and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/dunedin.html</link>
     <title>Dunedin Tourism Guide, Otago Peninsula Visitor Information, Attractions, Accommodation</title>
     <description>Dunedin tourism guide including Otago Peninsula travel and visitor information.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/fiordland.html</link>
     <title>Fiordland Tourism Guide, Milford Sound Te Anau Visitor Information, Attractions, Accommodation</title>
     <description>Fiordland tourism guide including Milford Sound, Te Anau visitor information, attractions, accommodation and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/franz-josef-fox-glacier.html</link>
     <title>Fox Glacier, Franz Josef Glacier Tourism Guide, visitor information, West Coast Glaciers</title>
     <description>Fox Glacier and Franz Josef Glacier tourism guide including visitor information on the west coast glaciers.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/hanmer-springs.html</link>
     <title>Hanmer Springs Tourism Guide, Hamner Springs travel visitor information, thermal reserve, Hot Pools</title>
     <description>Hanmer Springs New Zealand tourism guide including hamner springs thermal reserve hot pools visitor information.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/kaikoura.html</link>
     <title>Kaikoura Tourism guide, Kaikoura Visitor Information, Attractions, Accommodation</title>
     <description>Kaikoura tourism guide to visiting Kaikoura, whale watching, attractions, accommodation and other visitor information.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/lake-tekapo.html</link>
     <title>Lake Tekapo Tourism Guide, Tekapo visitor information, attractions, accommodation, flights</title>
     <description>Lake Tekapo tourism guide including Tekapo visitor information, attractions, accommodation and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/mt-cook.html</link>
     <title>Mount Cook Tourism Guide, Mt Cook Tasman Glacier, New Zealand's Tallest Mountain</title>
     <description>Mount Cook tourism guide including Mt Cook visitor attractions, Tasman Glacier Lake Tours, tourist attractions and NZ's tallest mountain.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/nelson.html</link>
     <title>Nelson Tourism guide, Nelson Lakes visitor attractions, accommodation information</title>
     <description>Nelson tourism guide including Nelson Lakes visitor attractions, accommodation and other information.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/oamaru-waitaki-valley.html</link>
     <title>Oamaru Tourism Guide, Waitaki Valley attractions, Moeraki Boulders, Blue Penguins</title>
     <description>Oamaru tourism guide along with Waitaki Valley attractions Moeraki Boulders and Blue Penguins.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/queenstown.html</link>
     <title>Queenstown Tourism Guide, Queenstown Visitor Information, Attractions Activities Accommodation</title>
     <description>Queenstown tourism guide including Queenstown visitor information, attractions activities accommodation and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/southland.html</link>
     <title>Southland Tourism Guide, Invercargill Visitor Information, The Catlins attractions, Accommodation, Bluff</title>
     <description>Southland tourism guide including Invercargill visitor information, attractions, accommodation, the Catlins, Bluff and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/twizel-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Twizel Attractions, Twizel tourist attractions, tourism guide, visitor information</title>
     <description>Twizel attractions including Twizel tourist attractions, tourism guide and visitor information.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/wanaka.html</link>
     <title>Lake Wanaka tourism guide, Wanaka visitor information, attractions, accommodation</title>
     <description>Lake Wanaka tourism guide including Wanaka visitor Information, attractions, accommodation and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/west-coast.html</link>
     <title>West Coast NZ Tourism Guide, Westland visitor Information, Pancake Rocks Attractions, Accommodation</title>
     <description>West Coast NZ tourism guide including Westland visitor information, Pancake Rocks Punakaiki, attractions, accommodation and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/stewart-island.html</link>
     <title>Stewart Island Tourism Guide, Travel to Stewart Island Visitor Information</title>
     <description>Stewart Island tourism guide including visitor information on travel to Stewart Island.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/attractions.html</link>
     <title>New Zealand Attractions, New Zealand tourist attractions, Activities, things to do</title>
     <description>New Zealand Attractions including New Zealand tourist attractions, activities, things to do in NZ, sightseeing options plus more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/auckland-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Auckland Attractions, Auckland Tourist Attractions, Sightseeing, Visitor Activities</title>
     <description>Auckland Attractions including Auckland Tourist Attractions sightseeing and visitor activities.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/bay-of-plenty-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Bay of Plenty Tourist Attractions, Tauranga, Mt Maunganui, White Island Visitor Attractions Activities</title>
     <description>Bay of Plenty Tourist Attractions including Tauranga Mount Maunganui Whakatane White Island visitor attractions and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/coromandel-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Coromandel Tourist Attractions, Cathedral Cove, Hot Water Beach Attractions, Pauanui, Thames, Waihi</title>
     <description>Coromandel Tourist Attractions including Cathedral Cove Hot Water Beach Pauanui Whangamata Thames and Waihi tourism guide.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/eastland-hawkes-bay-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Hawke's Bay Tourist Attractions, Hawkes Bay visitor activities things to do, Hastings, Napier, Gisborne, attactions</title>
     <description>Hawke's Bay tourist attractions including Hawkes bay visitor activities things to do in Hastings Napier Gisborne attactions.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/northland-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Northland Tourist Attractions, Cape Reinga, Bay of Islands Attractions, Paihia, Russell, Ninety Mile Beach</title>
     <description>Northland Tourist Attractions including Bay of Islands Attractions, Cape Reinga, Paihia Visitor Activities, Russell and Ninety Mile Beach.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/rotorua-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Rotorua Tourist Attractions, Rotorua Attractions Geysers, Geothermal Pools, Lake Rotorua, activities</title>
     <description>Rotorua Tourist Attractions including Rotorua Attractions Geysers, Geothermal pools and Lake Rotorua visitor activities.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/taranaki-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Taranaki Attractions, New Plymouth tourist attractions, visitor activities, Mt Taranaki tourism attractions, Walks, Surfing</title>
     <description>Taranaki attractions guide including New Plymouth tourist attractions visitor activities, Mt Taranki walks, surfing and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/taupo-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Taupo Tourist Attractions, Lake Taupo Attractions Activities Tongariro National Park</title>
     <description>Taupo Tourist Attractions including Lake Taupo Attractions, activities Tongariro National Park and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/waikato-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Waikato Tourist Attractions, Hamilton Attractions Activities Waitomo Caves Hamilton Gardens Hobbiton</title>
     <description>Waikato Tourist Attractions including Hamilton Attractions activities Waitomo Caves Hamilton Gardens, Hobbiton tours, Waikato museum and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/wellington-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Wellington Tourist Attractions in Wellington Attractions, Sightseeing visitor activities Guide</title>
     <description>Wellington Tourist Attractions including Wellington Attractions Guide, visitor activities and sightseeing.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/abel-tasman-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Abel Tasman Tourist Attractions, Golden Bay Attractions Visitor Guide, Farewell Spit</title>
     <description>Abel Tasman tourist attractions including Golden Bay visitor guide Farewell Spit Abel Tasman walkway, kayaking and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/akaroa-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Akaroa Attractions, Banks Peninsula Tourist Attractions, Tourism Activities Guide</title>
     <description>Akaroa tourist attractions guide including travel and tourism guide to Banks Peninsula area.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/blenheim-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Blenheim Attractions, Wine Tasting, Marlborough Tourist Attractions, Vineyard Tours, Activities</title>
     <description>Blenheim Attractions including Wine Tasting, tourist attractions, Wine Tours, Vineyard Tours in Marlborough.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/central-otago-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Central Otago Attractions, Rail Trail Tourist Attractions Mountain Biking Tours, Railtrail, gold mining, Alexandra Tourism, Cromwell</title>
     <description>Central Otago Attractions including the rail trail mountain biking tourist attractions in Alexandra along with Cromwell, Naseby &amp; Clyde.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/christchurch-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Christchurch Attractions, Christchurch Tourist Attractions, Sightseeing Visitor Activities Guide</title>
     <description>Christchurch Attractions including Christchurch tourist attractions and sightseeing visitor activities.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/dunedin-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Dunedin Tourist Attractions, Otago Peninsula Attractions, wildlife tours, Albatross Colony, Yellow eyed Penguins</title>
     <description>Dunedin Tourist Attractions including Otago Peninsula Attractions guide, wildlife tours plus the Royal Albatross Colony and Yellow eyed Penguins.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/fiordland-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Fiordland Attractions, Milford Sound Tourist Attractions, Boat Cruises, Doubtful Sound, Kayaking</title>
     <description>Fordland Attractions including Milford Sound Tourist Attractions scenic Doubtful Sound Boat cruises plus sea kayaking adventures and experiences.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/franz-josef-fox-glacier-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Franz Josef Glacier Tourist Attractions, Fox Glacier attractions, hiking, guided walks, Scenic Flights</title>
     <description>Franz Josef Glacier Tourist Attractions including Fox glacier Attractions hiking, guided walks and scenic helicopter flights.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/hanmer-springs-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Hanmer Springs Tourist Attractions, Hamner Springs Attractions, Thermal Pools Hot Springs</title>
     <description>Hanmer Springs Tourist Attractions including Hamner Springs Attractions, Thermal Pools and Hot Springs activities guide.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/kaikoura-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Kaikoura Attractions, Whale Watch Kaikoura, tourist attractions Dolphins birds kayaking visitor guide</title>
     <description>Kaikoura Attractions including Whale Watching Kaikoura tourist attractions, dolphins birds tours plus sea kayaking scenic flights.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/lake-tekapo-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Lake Tekapo Tourist Attractions, Visitor Attractions, Tekapo Scenic Flights, Hot Pools, Skiing</title>
     <description>Lake Tekapo Tourist Attractions including scenic walks, flights Tekapo hot pools ice skating mountain biking tours snow and water skiing.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/marlborough-sounds-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Marlborough Sounds Attractions, Queen Charlotte Track, Tourist Attractions, walks, Fishing, Tours, Boating</title>
     <description>Marlborough Sounds Attractions including Queen Charlotte Track, tourist attractions Dolphin Watch Eco tours, Kayaking and Boating.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/mt-cook-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Aoraki / Mount Cook Attractions, Mt Cook Tourist Attractions, Tasman Glacier Explorers Boat Tours, Climbing, Hiking, Scenic Flights</title>
     <description>Aoraki / Mount Cook Attractions including Mt Cook Tourist Attractions such as the Tasman Glacier Explorers Boat Tours, walks, Mountain Climbing and Scenic Flights.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/nelson-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Nelson Tourist Attractions, Skydiving, Scenic Flights, Mountain Biking, Horse treks, boating</title>
     <description>Nelson Tourist Attractions including skydiving, boating, mounatin biking, scenic flights, horse treks and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/oamaru-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Oamaru Tourist Attractions, Moeraki Boulders, Blue Penguins, Attractions Waitaki Valley</title>
     <description>Oamaru Tourist Attractions including Moeraki Boulders, Blue Penguins and attractions in the Waitaki Valley attractions.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/queenstown-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Queenstown Attractions, Queenstown Tourist Attractions, Activities, Bungy Jumping, Jet Boating, Wine Tours, Hiking</title>
     <description>Queenstown Attractions Guide including Queenstown tourist attractions bungy jumping Jet boating hiking and other adventure tourism activities.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/southland-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Southland Tourist Attractions, Invercargill attractions, Bluff, the Catlins, Hump Ridge Track</title>
     <description>Southland Tourist Attractions guide including Invercargill attractions, bluff, the Catlins, Hump Ridge track visitors guide.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/wanaka-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Wanaka Attractions, Lake Wanaka Tourist Attractions, Sightseeing, visitor activities Guide</title>
     <description>Wanaka Attractions including lake Wanaka tourist attractions, visitor activities and sightseeing guide.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/west-coast-attractions.html</link>
     <title>West Coast Attractions, Westland tourist attractions, Punakaiki Pancake Rocks, activities Hokitika Jade carving</title>
     <description>West Coast Attractions including westland tourist attractions Punakaiki Pancake Rocks activities Hokitika Punakaiki and Jade carving.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/stewart-island-attractions.html</link>
     <title>Stewart Island Tourist Attractions, Kiwi Spotting, walks, hiking, tours, Activities</title>
     <description>Stewart Island tourist attractions guide including activities such as walks, hiking kayaking Kiwi spotting wilderness guided tours plus more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/accommodation.html</link>
     <title>New Zealand Accommodation, Accomodation in New Zealand, Motels, Hotels</title>
     <description>New Zealand Accommodation including New Zealand apartments motels hotels accomodation bed and breakfasts holiday parks plus more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/auckland-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Auckland Accommodation, Hotels, Auckland Apartments, Motels Accommodation Guide</title>
     <description>Auckland Accommodation including Hotels, Auckland apartments motels and other accomodation.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/bay-of-plenty-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Bay of Plenty Accommodation, Mt Maunganui apartments, Tauranga Hotels Whakatane Motels, holiday parks</title>
     <description>Bay of Plenty accommodation including Mt Maunganui apartments Tauranga hotels Whakatane Motels plus holiday parks.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/coromandel-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Coromandel Accommodation, Whitianga Apartments, Bed and Breakfasts Lodges Holiday Parks</title>
     <description>Coromandel accommodation including Whitianga apartments bed and breakfast lodges holiday parks plus more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/eastland-hawkes-bay-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Napier Accommodation, Napier, Gisborne Hotels, Hastings Motels, Motor Lodges</title>
     <description>Napier accommodation including Napier motels, accomodation Gisborne, Hotels in Hastings motels plus motor lodges and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/taranaki-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>New Plymouth Accommodation, New Plymouth Hotels Motels Accomodation, Bed and Breakfasts</title>
     <description>New Plymouth Accommodation including New Plymouth hotels, motels, bed &amp; breakfasts plus other accomodation.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/northland-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Northland Accommodation, Bay of Islands Hotels, Paihia Motels, Russell Bed &amp; Breakfasts, Far North</title>
     <description>Northland accommodation including Bay of Islands hotels Paihia motels Russell bed and breakfasts plus far north holiday lodgings.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/rotorua-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Rotorua Accommodation, Rotorua Hotels, Motels, Holiday Parks, Lodges</title>
     <description>Rotorua Accommodation including Rotorua hotels motels apartments holiday parks and lodges.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/ruapehu-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Ohakune Accommodation, Mt Ruapehu Hotels, Whakapapa Apartments, Lodges Motels, Resorts</title>
     <description>Ohakune Accommodation including Mt Ruapehu hotels Whakapapa village apartments, motels lodges &amp; resorts.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/taupo-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Taupo Accommodation, Lake Taupo accomodation, Hotels, Motels, Lodges</title>
     <description>Taupo Accommodation including Lake Taupo accomodation, Hotels, Motels and Lodges.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/hamilton-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Hamilton Accommodation, Hamilton Hotels, Motels, Waitomo Holiday Parks</title>
     <description>Hamilton accommodation including Hamilton hotels motels, Waitomo holiday park accomodation, Motor-Inns and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/wellington-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Wellington Accommodation, Wellington Hotels, Apartments, Bed and Breakfasts</title>
     <description>Wellington accommodation including wellington hotels apartments bed &amp; breakfasts and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/abel-tasman-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Abel Tasman Accommodation, Marahau Accommodation in Motueka, Golden Bay</title>
     <description>Abel Tasman Accommodation including Marahau Accomodation in Motueka, Kaiteriteri and Golden Bay.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/akaroa-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Akaroa Accommodation, Akaroa Apartments, Motels, Bed and Breakfasts, Farmstay</title>
     <description>Akaroa Accommodation including Akaroa apartments motels bed and breakfasts &amp; farmstay lodgings.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/blenheim-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Blenheim Accommodation, Blenheim Hotels, Motels, homestays bed and breakfasts, Cottages</title>
     <description>Blenheim Accommodation including blenheim hotels motels homestays bed breakfasts and cottages.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/central-otago-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Central Otago Accommodation, Alexandra Bed &amp; Breakfast Cromwell Hotels Wedderburn</title>
     <description>Central Otago Accommodation including Alexandra bed &amp; breakfasts, motels, Cromwell hotels, Wedderburn Rail Trail lodgings and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/christchurch-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Christchurch Accommodation, Christchurch Hotels, Motels, Bed &amp; Breakfasts</title>
     <description>Christchurch accommodation including Christchurch Hotels Motels plus apartments Bed &amp; breakfasts and holiday park.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/dunedin-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Dunedin Accommodation, Otago Peninsula, Dunedin Motels, Apartments, Hotels</title>
     <description>Dunedin accommodation including Otago Peninsula accomodation Dunedin motels apartments hotels and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/fiordland-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Milford Sound Accommodation, Te Anau Hotels, Motels Bed and breakfast</title>
     <description>Milford Sound Accommodation including Lake Te Anau Hotels Motels bed &amp; breakfasts plus holiday parks.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/franz-josef-fox-glacier-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Franz Josef Glacier Accommodation, Fox Glacier accommodation,Franz Joseph Accomodation</title>
     <description>Franz Josef Glacier Accommodation plus Fox Glacier accomodation including apartments, Hotels Franz Joseph motels and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/hanmer-springs-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Hanmer Springs Accommodation Hamner Springs Motels, Holiday homes houses, Apartments, bed and breakfasts</title>
     <description>Hanmer Springs accommodation guide including Hamner Springs motels, holiday homes houses, apartments plus bed and breakfast lodgings.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/kaikoura-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Kaikoura Accommodation, Kaikoura Lodges, Motels, Apartments, Bed and Breakfast</title>
     <description>Kaikoura accommodation including Kaikoura Motels bed &amp; breakfasts apartments camping ground accomodation plus more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/lake-tekapo-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Tekapo Accommodation, Lake Tekapo Motels, Apartments, Bed and Breakfasts, holiday homes Holiday Park Hotel</title>
     <description>Tekapo Accommodation including Lake Tekapo motels, hotels, bed &amp; breakfasts, camping grounds, holiday homes and houses.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/marlborough-sounds-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Marlborough Sounds Accommodation, Picton Motels, Queen Charlotte Sound Resorts Holiday houses Bed and Breakfasts</title>
     <description>Marlborough Sounds Accommodation including Picton motels plus Queen Charlotte Sound Resorts holiday homes &amp; Bed and Breakfasts.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/mt-cook-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Aoraki Mt Cook Accommodation, Mount Cook Hotels, Motels, Lodges, Holiday Parks</title>
     <description>Aoraki Mt Cook Accommodation including Mount Cook Hotels Motels Lodges holiday parks tenting powered sites camping grounds cabins plus more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/nelson-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Nelson Accommodation, Nelson Lakes Lodges, Motels, Apartments, Hotels, Motueka Bed &amp; Breakfasts</title>
     <description>Nelson accommodation including Nelson lakes lodges motels apartments hotels plus Motueka bed and breakfasts.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/oamaru-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Oamaru Accommodation, Oamaru Motels, Bed &amp; Breakfasts Lodge, Hotels</title>
     <description>Oamaru Accommodation including Oamaru motels bed and breakfasts Country Lodges plus Hotels.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/queenstown-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Queenstown Accommodation, Queenstown Apartments, Hotels, Motels Bed and Breakfasts</title>
     <description>Queenstown Accommodation guide including Queenstown apartments, hotels, bed and breakfasts and motels.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/southland-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Invercargill Accommodation, Hotels, Motels, apartments, Catlins, B&amp;B's Apartments</title>
     <description>Invercargill accommodation including hotels motels apartments Catlins B&amp;B's and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/twizel-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Twizel accommodation, Twizel hotels Lodges, motels, accomodation, Bed and Breakfasts</title>
     <description>Twizel accommodation including twizel hotels, accomodation, lodges motels in Twizel, bed and breakfasts and more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/wanaka-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Wanaka Accommodation, Wanaka Apartments, Hotels, Lodges, Bed and Breakfasts Holiday Homes</title>
     <description>Wanaka accommodation including Wanaka apartments hotels lodges bed and breakfasts motels accomodation plus holiday homes &amp; houses.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/west-coast-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>West Coast Accommodation, Hokitika Punakaiki Motels, Greymouth Hotels, Lodges Westport, Westland</title>
     <description>West Coast accommodation including Hokitika Punakaiki lodges Greymouth Hotels motels Westland accomodation bed &amp; breakfasts plus more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/stewart-island-accommodation.html</link>
     <title>Stewart Island Accommodation, Stewart Island Hotels, Motels, Apartments</title>
     <description>Stewart Island accommodation including Stewart Island Hotels Motels apartments lodges retreats plus more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/tours.html</link>
     <title>Custom New Zealand Tours, Packaged tours to suit your budget, cycling, biking, walking, hiking</title>
     <description>Custom New Zealand tours including packaged tours to suit your budget such as self-drive sightseeing NZ wine tour guide plus coach, cycling / biking motorcycle touring &amp; more.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/campervans.html</link>
     <title>New Zealand Campervans for hire, New Zealand Motorhomes, Camper Vans, Motorhome Rentals NZ</title>
     <description>New Zealand Campervans for hire including New Zealand Motorhomes Camper vans Rentals, Motorhome hire &amp; NZ campers.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/rental-cars.html</link>
     <title>New Zealand Rental Cars, Car Hire, Car Rentals New Zealand</title>
     <description>New Zealand Rental Cars Guide including car hire, car rentals in New Zealand.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/contact.html</link>
     <title>Contact Us</title>
     <description>Contact us, enquiries, Contact us at NZ Escape</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/sitemap.html</link>
     <title>Site Map  Page 1 - Generated by www.xml-sitemaps.com</title>
     <description>Site Map  Page 1 - Generated by www.xml-sitemaps.com</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/about-nz.html</link>
     <title>Information about New Zealand, General Info about NZ, Facts and Figures</title>
     <description>Information about New Zealand. Facts and figures about NZ.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>2</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.nzescape.com/advertising.html</link>
     <title>New Zealand Tourism Advertising, Promote your Tourism Business with NZ Escape</title>
     <description>New Zealand tourism advertising including online tourism promotion and internet marketing on the net.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>daily</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>2</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
  